CHALERMKHWAN NASRITHA

Front-End Developer

SUMMARY

Frontend web developer with 3 years of work experience in developing and maintaining React applications. Fast learner with an ability to collaborate effectively across team and solve problems. Seeking an opportunity to join a team of talented like-minded individuals to work and grow with.

SKILLS

Front-End Development:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React.js, Next.js

Testing and CI/CD:

Cypress, Jest, ESLint, Docker, Spinnaker, Jenkins, Dynatrace, OpenSearch

Version Control, Cloud, and Tools:

Git, Gitlab, Github, AWS S3, AWS Lambda, Visual Studio, Pimcore CMS

EDUCATION

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang, Bangkok, Thailand

Bachelors of Computer Engineering (June 2010 – March 2014)

CONTACT

Number: 224-245-5354

Email: chalermkhwan.b.n@gmail.com **Website:** www.chalermkhwan.com **Github:** github.com/khwaniiz

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Intelsat (08/2021- Present)

- Collaborate with third parties to implement, enhance, integrate and maintain features using React to increase customer engagement and revenue.
- Support, monitor, and debug frontend issues during the development and deployment processes.
- Monitor and update frontend applications for compliance with latest dependencies.
- Conduct regular team code reviews to ensure conformance with best practices.
- Work with designers to implement UI/UX layouts and provide feedback for optimal user experience.
- Coordinate with backend team to integrate frontend and backend functions.
- Use Dynatrace to log data, errors and metrics to ensure proper application functionality.

Front-End Internship

Minority Programmers Association (05/03/2021- 07/30/2021) https://minorityprogrammers.com/

- Work in an Agile development cycle using Scrum methodologies
- Develop responsive web application for Homepage, Incubator and Voter pages from Figma wireframe using Next.js framework.
- Implement dynamic routing and data fetching from API using Next.js framework.
- Use Context API to maintain user state through application.
- Collaborate with product team members to implement features.
- Work with mentors on development projects for the website throughout the various phases of the project life cycle.
- Maintain/update existing code and functionality.

PROJECTS

https://keenokthai.netlify.app/

- Responsive web development for compatibility with mobile devices
- Development of mailing list web application using MailChimp API + Node.js

Food Ordering E-commerce Project

https://www.keenokthai.com/

 React application integrated with Node.js, MongoDB and Stripe payment with admin dashboard

